const defaultGameData = {
  boards: [
    {
      categories: [
        "HOMONYMS",
        "BOARD GAMES",
        "DROPS OF JUPITER",
        "JUMP FOR JOY",
        "_A_A_A",
      ],
      questions: [
        [
          {
            points: 200,
            question:
              "What someone in a bowling alley or on a pitcher's mound hopes to throw.",
            answer: "What is a strike?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 400,
            question: "A line of seats in a theater or a quarrel.",
            answer: "What is a row?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 600,
            question: "16 American ounces or 100 British pence.",
            answer: "What is a pound?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 800,
            question: "The front of a ship or to bend forward in respect.",
            answer: "What is a bow?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 1000,
            question:
              "A loud, unpleasant noise or a fraudulent scheme to get money.",
            answer: "What is a racket?",
            revealed: false,
          },
        ],
        [
          {
            points: 200,
            question:
              "This murder mystery game was invented during WWII air raids by Anthony Pratt to pass time, with original pieces made of toxic lead.",
            answer: "What is Clue (or Cluedo)",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 400,
            question:
              "While it was popular in Cuba, Fidel Castro shamed this game as being 'symbolic of an imperialistic and capitalistic system'",
            answer: "What is Monopoly?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 600,
            question:
              "Two skydivers played this letter-based game while falling from 13,000 feet to celebrate its 60th birthday in 2008.",
            answer: "What is Scrabble?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 800,
            question:
              "The Taliban banned this ancient strategy game in Afghanistan in 2025, claiming it promotes gambling under Islamic law.",
            answer: "What is Chess?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 1000,
            question:
              "This game invented in 1860 originally included squares for 'Suicide', 'Disgrace', 'Poverty', and 'Prison'.",
            answer: "What is The Game of Life?",
            revealed: false,
          },
        ],
        [
          {
            points: 200,
            question:
              "This colorfully named region of Jupiter produces wind-speeds up to 432 kmph (268 mph).",
            answer: "What is the Great Red Spot?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 400,
            question:
              "Jupiter is made up mostly of these gases, the first 2 elements on the periodic table",
            answer: "What are hydrogen and helium?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 600,
            question:
              "Named for a Trojan hero, it's the largest of Jupiter's Galilean moons, which is also the largest moon in the solar system",
            answer: "What is Ganymede?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 800,
            question:
              "It takes over 11 years for Jupiter to orbit the Sun at 5.2 AU, short for these",
            answer: "What are astronomical units?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 1000,
            question:
              "Jupiter's rings were discovered in 1979 by this interstellar probe that contained a golden record",
            answer: "What is Voyager 1?",
            revealed: false,
          },
        ],
        [
          {
            points: 200,
            question: "This toy is essential to playing Double Dutch.",
            answer: "What is a jump rope?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 400,
            question:
              "If your car's battery dies, hope you have a pair of these.",
            answer: "What are jumper cables?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 600,
            question:
              "A 2012 film adaptation of this Fox show starred Channing Tatum and Jonah Hill",
            answer: "What is 21 Jump Street?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 800,
            question:
              "'Roots' is responsible for reviving this African-American wedding custom.",
            answer: "What is jumping the broom?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 1000,
            question:
              "Carl Boenish is considered the father of the modern version of this extreme sport",
            answer: "What is BASE jumping?",
            revealed: false,
          },
        ],
        [
          {
            points: 200,
            question:
              "A region bounded by the Mediterranean Coastal region to the north, and the Sahel to the south.",
            answer: "What is the Sahara?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 400,
            question:
              "After Santo Domingo, this capital city has the second most populous metropolitan area in the entire Caribbean",
            answer: "What is Havana?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 600,
            question:
              "First name of a female education activist who won the nobel peace prize",
            answer: "What is Malala?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 800,
            question:
              "A sword characterized by a curved, single edge blade with a long grip",
            answer: "What is a Katana?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 1000,
            question:
              "This large berry is ripe when it turns orange and has black seeds in its large central cavity",
            answer: "What is a Papaya?",
            revealed: false,
          },
        ],
      ],
    },
    {
      categories: [
        "MATH HOMONYMS",
        "TROUBLES & TREATIES",
        "KEEP IT 100",
        "ALL ABOUT U",
        "_A_A_A_"
      ],
      questions: [
        [
          {
            points: 400,
            question: "In number theory, the additive inverse of a positive number will always be this. In medicine, it's the result you usually want to get from a diagnostic test",
            answer: "What is negative?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 800,
            question: "In mathematics, it's a function that gives the principal value of a square root. In politics, it's disruptive and extreme.",
            answer: "What is radical?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 1200,
            question: "In geometry, it's a partial circumference of a circle. In literature, it's how a character changes over the course of a story.",
            answer: "What is an arc?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 1600,
            question: "In trigonometry, it's the determination of a length or coordinate based on other known points or segments. In psychology, it's the unwanted or harmful involvement of an outside party in a relationship.",
            answer: "What is triangulation?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 2000,
            question: "In complex systems, it's non-random but difficult or impossible to predict behavior. In general, it's just something disordered and out-of-control",
            answer: "What is chaos?",
            revealed: false,
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            points: 400,
            question: "From the Afrikaans for “separateness,” it was South Africa's policy of racial segregation.",
            answer: "What is apartheid?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 800,
            question: "The legal code of this 6th Babylonian king is inscribed on a basalt stele over 7 ft. tall",
            answer: "What is Hammurabi?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 1200,
            question: "191 countries have signed the U.N.'s greenhouse gas protocol named for this Japanese city.",
            answer: "What is Kyoto?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 1600,
            question: "A 2023 law in the U.K. began a process of reconciliation for this period of unrest in Northern Ireland",
            answer: "What is the Troubles?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 2000,
            question: "This 1919 act of Congress allowed for the enforcement of the 18th Amendment and Prohibition.",
            answer: "What is the Volstead Act?",
            revealed: false,
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            points: 400,
            question: "100 is the sum of the first 9 of these numbers, from 2 to 23.",
            answer: "What is a prime number?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 800,
            question: "It's easy to look this up online: it's 1 followed by 100 zeroes.",
            answer: "What is a googol?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 1200,
            question: "This Orson Welles masterpiece topped AFI's “100 Years....100 Movies” list in 2007.",
            answer: "What is Citizen Kane?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 1600,
            question: "On March 2, 1962, this “Stilt” became the first NBA player to score 100 points in a single game.",
            answer: "Who is Wilt Chamberlain?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 2000,
            question: "Before the euro's introduction in 2002, this Portuguese currency was divided into 100 centavos.",
            answer: "What is the escudo?",
            revealed: false,
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            points: 400,
            question: "The large pendulous organ that houses the mammary glands of cows.",
            answer: "What is an udder?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 800,
            question: "Existing or universally everywhere at the same time, or commonly encountered.",
            answer: "What is ubiquitous?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 1200,
            question: "The small bone on the pinkie side of your forearm.",
            answer: "What is the ulna?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 1600,
            question: "The Chinese Muslim minority that populates most of Chinese Turkestan.",
            answer: "What are the Uyghurs?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 2000,
            question: "To utter a loud, high-pitched, rhythmical sound especially as an expression of sorrow, joy, celebration, or reverence.",
            answer: "What is ululate?",
            revealed: false,
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            points: 400,
            question: "This holy month of communal prayer and reflection starts and ends at the sighting of a crescent moon",
            answer: "What is Ramadan?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 800,
            question: "An English scientist best known for his work in electrochemistry, and for having units of charge and capacitance named for him.",
            answer: "Who is Faraday?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 1200,
            question: "This word can either mean a single wheeled vehicle or a large group of people all traveling together.",
            answer: "What is a caravan?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 1600,
            question: "This is the only capital in South America without a US embassy.",
            answer: "What is Caracas?",
            revealed: false,
          },
          {
            points: 2000,
            question: "This type of purchase agreement where a seller reserves an object until full payment has been made has declined in practice since the introduction of credit cards.",
            answer: "What is a layaway?",
            revealed: false,
          }
        ]
      ],
    }
  ],
  defaultPlayers: [
    { name: "Player 1", score: 0 },
    { name: "Player 2", score: 0 },
  ],
};

// Export the game data
export { defaultGameData };
